<?xml version = "1.0" encoding = "UTF-8" ?>
<Computer id="SmokeMessaging" name="Smoke Internal Message Server" ip="104.73.110.243" type="0">
	
	<admin type="fast" resetPassword="false" isSuper="false"/>
	<portsForCrack val="5" />
	<ports>21,22,25,80,1433,3724</ports>
	<trace time="75" />
	<firewall level="11" solution="SUMMER0SALE" additionalTime="0.1"/>
	
	<file path="sys" name="Blizzard_Updater.dll">#BINARYSMALL#</file>
	<file path="sys" name="Blizzard_Configuration.cfg">Updater IP: 69.121.211.192
	Client ID: SmokeDistribution
	Client Pass: KZysazM6sTmyfBiX</file>
	
	<account username="R4D3473R" password="8Billi3n*LUMeNS" type="MAIL" />
	<account username="xx_Xenon_xx" password="313M3N7#54" type="MAIL" />
	
	<mailServer name="Smoke Messenger" color="32,48,128" generateJunk="true">
		<email recipient="R4D3473R" sender="xx_Xenon_xx" subject="Awesome new h4xx0r game!!">Hey, R4D!

I know you're in love with hacking games, and this one is free for 48 hours only!

It's this terminal-based hacking simulator called Hackent and it's the closest you'll ever be to being super 31337 like me.

LOL, x
		</email>
		<email recipient="xx_Xenon_xx" sender="R4D3473R" subject="re: Awesome new h4xx0r game!!">
Thanks!
I've actually had my eye on that one for a while; I got it as soon as the giveaway started.
On an unrelated note, I've forgotten the password that I set on my ePad before the summer.
I can access the files on it fine because it's synced to my computer...
Except I can't get at the stuff outside the normally accessible directories.
Dumb anti-jailbreak unfriendly design...
Anyway. You know me well. Can you think of what I may have used?
		</email>
		<email recipient="R4D3473R" sender="xx_Xenon_xx" subject="re: re: Awesome new h4xx0r game!!">
You insult me. Implying the best I can do is guess your password...

...

Not really. But if you want me to break into your tablet to recover all your dirty documents, That's within my power.

Send me your IP. A password to your computer would be nice but it isn't necessary.

I'll reset the password on your ePad back to the factory default after I'm done snooping.

LOL, x
		</email>
		<email recipient="xx_Xenon_xx" sender="R4D3473R" subject="re: re: re: Awesome new h4xx0r game!!">
Oh.
uh, thanks?
I guess if you're able to, then go right ahead.
My IP is 234.183.63.109
I'm not sure how secure the Smoke messager is, so I don't really want to share my password over it...
Meh.
I'll probably end up changing all of my passwords anyway, so I guess it doesn't really matter what we say here.
My computer password is 1|21D35C3N7 but I'll change it immediately after you're done. 
		</email>
	</mailServer>
	
	<dlink target="SmokeDistribution" />
	
</Computer>